(Sheldon:)Fellow warriors,
this is Sheldor the Conqueror.
We are about to enter Atzel's fortress.
(Sheldon:)Now, this is a long run,
so let's do another bladder check.
All right, Barry, we'll wait for you again,
but you really should see a doctor.
[BANGING NEARBY]
(Sheldon:)Sheldor is AFK.
(Sheldon:)Penny, are you experiencing
some sort of difficulty?
(Penny:)Yes, I can't get my stupid door open.
(Sheldon:)You appear to have put your car key
in the door lock. Are you aware of that?
(Penny:)Yeah.
All right, then.
PENNY:
Damn it, damn it, damn it.
(Sheldon:)Would it be possible for you
to do this a little more quietly?
- I can't get the damn key out.
- That's not surprising.
(Sheldon:)That Baldwin lock on your door uses
traditional edge-mounted cylinders...
...whereas the key for your Volkswagen
uses a center-cylinder system.